energizerbunniesmommyreports.com 2017-09-15

# Privacy - Mommy Snippets

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Mommy Snippets has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Our Commitment To Childrens Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, Mommy Snippets will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.  
Under our Terms of Service, children under 18 are not allowed to access our service.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting Mommy Snippets , the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice visit the NAI at http://www.networkadvertising.org. To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit<http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.**

**When we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site, these companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:[http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)**

We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, one of which is [http://www.gourmetads.com](http://www.gourmetads.com/).

**Opt Out**

For information about opting out of Gourmet Ads and ad serving partners please visit <http://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy>

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please [contact us](http://girlraisedinthesouth.com/contact-us/ "contact us").

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Mommy Snippets then you may contact us at mjblog09@gmail.com
